damnlag.com 2013-09-04

# Video Game Opinion, Articles, Reviews, Editorials

**Overview**  
DamnLag presents this information to you regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from you.

**Participating Merchant Policies**  
Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in DamnLag services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

**Information We Collect and How We Use It**  
DamnLag collects certain information from and about its users three ways: directly from our Web Server logs, the user, and with Cookies.  
A. Web Server Logs  
When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:  
Your Internet protocol address  
The kind of browser or computer you use  
Number of links you click within the site  
State or country from which you accessed the site  
Date and time of your visit  
Name of your Internet service provider  
Web page you linked to our site from  
Pages you viewed on the site  
B. Use of Cookies  
DamnLag may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality.

DamnLag reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies, but does not allow other companies to place cookies on our website unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value (such as merging into DamnLag technologies that relies on third-party cookies).  
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.

C. Personal Information Users

Visitors to our website can register to purchase services. When you register, we will request some personal information such as name, address, email, telephone number or facsimile number, account number and other relevant information. If you are purchasing a service, we will request financial information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. For other types of registrations, we will ask for the relevant information. You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be warranted in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting.

We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:

To fulfill your service requests for services.  
To protect ourselves from liability,  
To respond to legal process or comply with law, or  
In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.

**Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

**Web Beacons (Clear GIFs, Pixel Tags)**

We may employ and our third party partners may employ a software technology called web beacons, also referred to as clear GIFs or pixel tags, that help manage content on the Service by tracking what content is effective. Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of users in order to further personalize our Service for our users and to collect a limited set of information about our users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We also may include web beacons in advertisements or promotional or other e-­‐mail messages or to determine whether messages have been opened or acted upon. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

**Changes in this Privacy Policy**

DamnLag may, in its sole discretion, from time to time, modify or revise this Privacy Policy without notice, and you agree to be bound by such modifications or revisions. The most current version of this Privacy Policy can be viewed at our website. Once posted, our amended Privacy Policy will take become effective on a going forward basis as provided in the Terms of Service, except that (i) unless you agree otherwise, we will use your personally identifiable information in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when we received that information and (ii) if you do not agree with any changes to the Privacy Policy, you may terminate your account and cease use of the Service. Your continued use of the Service after revised Privacy Policy has become effective indicates that you have read, understood and agreed to the current version of the Privacy Policy.

**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions about these Terms of Service, please contact DamnLag at support@damnlag.com.
